export const data = [
  {
    question: "Who developed React.js?",
    options: ["Apple", "Facebook", "Google", "Twitter"],
    correctOption: "Facebook",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of react.js developer?",
    options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Lee", "Jordan Walke", "Time Lee"],
    correctOption: "Jordan Walke",
  },
  {
    question: "Everything in React is a _______.",
    options: ["Module", "Component", "Package", "Class"],
    correctOption: "Component",
  },
  {
    question: "How many elements does a react component returns?",
    options: [
      "Only One Element",
      "Only Two Elements",
      "Multiple Elements",
      "None",
    ],
    correctOption: "Multiple Elements",
  },
  {
    question: "In which directory React Components are saved?",
    options: [
      "Inside js/components/",
      "Inside vendor/components/",
      "Inside external/components/",
      "Inside Vendor",
    ],
    correctOption: "Inside js/components/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    options: [
      "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
      " Server side Framework",
      "User-interface framework",
      "None",
    ],
    correctOption: "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
  },
  {
    question: "In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?",
    options: ["setState", "render with arguments", "propTypes", "props"],
    correctOption: "props",
  },
  {
    question: "Props are ______ into other components.",
    options: ["Methods", "Injected", "Both 1 & 2", "None"],
    correctOption: "Methods",
  },
  {
    question: "ReactJS uses ________ to increase performance.",
    options: ["Original DOM", "Virtual DOM", "Both 1 & 2", "None of above"],
    correctOption: "Virtual DOM",
  },
  {
    question: "________ helps react for keeping their data unidirectional.",
    options: ["Flux", "JSX", "DOM", "Props"],
    correctOption: "Flux",
  },
];
